[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 13]
I've checked the inn's ledger.
It shows that nine days ago,
Gao Sheng had stayed at this inn
for four consecutive days.
But the innkeeper and his staff
had all told me
they've never seen this person.
This inn is indeed strange.
The Cat Demon
that led us here before
appeared again last night.
It led us to the Xin Court.
At that place, we found
Banxia's cousin.
Banxia's cousin?
Yes.
He seems to know something,
but he won't say it.
So, is the culprit
a demon or a human after all?
Feng Tian said
he was once a border guard,
guarding the border alone for twenty years.
Would such a person kill?
That's not necessarily true.
Maybe he's lying to you.
What about that Cat Demon then?
I'm not sure about
its intentions yet.
But I have a feeling
that besides this Cat Demon and Feng Tian,
there's something else
hidden in this inn.
It's just that we
haven't discovered it yet.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel like
there's been something
watching me lately.
Physician Jiu,
Youhuang said you have the ability
to catch demons and monsters.
Do you have any
demon-suppressing or evil-repelling items
to give me some courage?
No.
Come on, find me some.
Let's go.
Where to?
Didn't you say Banxia's cousin
seems to know something?
Let's go ask him.
Chief.
Honored guest.
Honored guest,
someone is looking for you in the front courtyard.
Who is it?
Looks like a villager from down the mountain.
He seems quite urgent.
You'd better go check quickly.
Villager?
You're looking for me?
Are you Chu Youhuang,
Chief Constable Chu?
I am. What's the matter?
I went up the mountain early this morning
and found a body near the cliff.
There was this letter on the body.
The letter mentions
the Reunion Inn and you, Chief Constable Chu.
So I thought I'd come and ask.
This is the letter I wrote to Lord Geng.
Chief,
something happened to Yan Li.
Where's the body?
It's right by the cliff.
Take us there.
Alright.
Where is it?
It's right there.
Yan Li.
Chief.
This.
Yan Li.
What happened?
His neck was snapped.
Who did this?
Daring to attack an official.
It's truly audacious.
They'd better not let me catch them.
Chief.
His son just turned one month old.
They haven't even had the full moon celebration yet.
Enough.
Ji Nu'er.
The swallow you gave me is really beautiful.
Wuniang.
Get out.
I need to ask you something.
You must answer truthfully.
Did you
kill that guy?
No.
I haven't even said who it was yet
and you're already saying no?
No matter who it is,
I didn't kill them.
Father, don't you believe me?
Talking back to me?
If you don't believe me, Father,
you might as well turn me in.
Aren't there constables at the shop?
You can hand me over to them.
That would solve it, wouldn't it?
That's not what I meant.
Tell me.
Did you do it?
Why do you look like
you wish I had killed him, Father?
Fine.
I'll kill someone
to fulfill your wish then!
Don't be ridiculous.
Father.
Do you know me at all?
Wuniang.
I just want you to
live a peaceful life.
I won't bring shame to you, that's all.
Wuniang.
Can't you be a bit more obedient?
I just want what's best for you.
Alright.
Yanqiu, it's me, Banxia.
I‘ll head out now.
Yanqiu.
I thought you weren't in your room.
Why didn't you answer
when I knocked earlier?
Arm in arm while we come and go.
Lingering close by your knee below.
Well sung.
Yanqiu.
What are you doing?
Banxia, you're here.
Have a seat.
Let's listen to music together.
Cousin, what are you staring at?
Your sister-in-law.
Yanqiu.
What on earth are you talking about?
She can't handle it.
She can't bear to hear this.
Your sister-in-law laughs that you're just a little girl,
not used to hearing these tunes
about frontier travel
that are full of panic and chaos.
She wants to sing you
a lighter, more melodious love poem.
Han Guang: Tall Trees in the South.
Have you heard it before?
♫There are tall trees in the south♫
♫But they offer no rest♫
♫There are beautiful wandering girls by the Han River♫
♫But they cannot be pursued♫
♫The Han River is so wide, it cannot be swum across♫
♫The Yangtze flows so long♫
♫It cannot be crossed from any direction♫
Banxia.
Be careful.
How is it?
I'll go get you water to wipe your face.
Come, come.
Keep me company to drink wine
and listening to music.
How did you discover him?
Reporting to Chief Constable Chu,
this place, usually,
has very few people and a lot of firewood.
I...
I came here to chop wood.
Don't leave the village recently.
You can go back now.
Yes.
Yan Li's martial skills are quite good.
Even if he couldn't defeat a strong enemy,
he should have been able to escape.
This criminal's grip strength is incredible.
The flesh on his back
was completely torn off.
What kind of person
would do such a thing?
In such remote mountains,
who could know?
Unless...
Yan Li could speak.
You can't go in.
This is my family's inn.
Why can't I enter?
You still can't go in.
Fine, I won't go in then.
What's the big deal?
How could you do this?
I... I've already come in.
What more do you want?
Banxia, she tricked me.
Oh, Miss Duan is here too.
Why are you here?
I came to bring wine for Mr. Duan.
Didn't I tell you?
Ever since he arrived,
he's been staying in his room all day,
just drinking wine.
Didn't you tell me before
that you hardly ever saw him
and that you almost forgot about him?
Before, it was the servants taking care of him.
But I heard
that he's your cousin.
So, I came personally.
Wait a moment.
What exactly is this?
This is Fubai Wine.
Haven't you heard of it, Miss Duan?
The guests who come here
all really like this wine.
They say that after drinking it,
they could see
the person they miss the most.
Miss Duan,
would you like some?
There was only one assailant.
His foot measures eight inches and two tenths.
About seven feet tall. Male.
He was young.
But he was heavy.
Must be a fat guy.
Not necessarily.
Although he wasn't agile,
he was physically strong.
If he were fat,
he couldn't have been so quick.
He should be of medium build,
a physically strong man.
He didn't carry any weapons.
Yan Li was skilled in martial arts.
If he could be killed barehanded,
could the assailant be
someone with exceptional martial arts skills?
No.
He was stabbed.
But why isn't there
any trace of blood on the ground?
Perhaps it was cleaned up.
Or perhaps he was wearing an armour.
That's why his body was so heavy.
He tore off Yan Li's skin with his bare hands.
This method is too cruel.
He seemed completely unafraid of
Yan Li's resistance.
It was as if he was toying with
a plaything.
This strangulation mark...
He's missing a finger on his right hand.
I'm just a bit dizzy.
I'll be fine after a short rest.
Please don't worry about it.
That person is in the inn.
I've seen him.
What's this?
From now on,
don't bring this kind of wine anymore.
If customers want to drink,
we have no reason not to sell it.
Yanqiu is now
in a daze and unclear every day.
I am his sister.
I have the right to make decisions for him.
If you bring this wine again,
don't blame me for getting angry with you.
Alright, if you don't want it, I won't bring it.
Please don't be angry, Miss Duan.
Take them away quickly.
Miss Duan.
Liar.
I was just teasing you.
You really got angry?
What happened to your neck?
I have something to do.
I'm not playing with you anymore.
Let's go.
Sir, sir.
Put it down first.
Everything has been taken care of.
It seems the innkeeper
is very concerned about my colleague.
Yes, indeed.
Put it down first.
After all,
it's a human life.
Is that so?
If he were alive,
he would probably thank you in person.
Don't move.
Sir.
This person died outside.
Let's not bring him inside.
There are guests inside after all.
I am the Chief Constable of Guangping City.
I suspect your inn
is connected to the murder
of my colleague.
From this moment on,
the inn is closed.
No one is allowed to enter or leave.
Do you understand?
You can't say that, sir.
The person died outside,
not inside my inn.
What does it have to do with us?
Moreover,
do you have any evidence?
With evidence, it's called solving a case.
Without evidence, it's called investigating a case.
Any objections?
Xuanye,
keep a close eye on things for me.
What's going on here?
I asked you to watch the inn earlier.
Have you seen a man
with only
four fingers on his right hand?
Yes, I have.
I just saw him.
He left with Wuniang.
Where did they go?
Follow me.
Alright.
Thank you, Wuniang.
Sir.
It's here.
Dear guests.
Where are you going?
To look for your servant.
If there's anything, just tell me.
Sir.
It's him.
This...
Mr. Jiu.
I clearly saw it.
Saw what?
He only has four fingers on his right hand.
Wh-what?
You must have seen wrong.
Impossible.
That's strange then.
He clearly has five fingers here.
That's right.
Sir.
What are you trying to do?
You're scaring her.
If you have any questions, talk to me.
Innkeeper, if you have nothing to hide,
why are you stopping me?
Do you know that harbouring is the same as being an accomplice?
Mr. Jiu,
you and your group
sought to lodge late at night.
I was the one who persuaded Father
to let you stay.
Now you're being so rude to us.
Don't you think your behaviour is inappropriate?
Don't be disrespectful.
Sir,
as you know,
my daughter has been sickly since childhood.
If we have offended you in any way,
please be understanding.
A fox will definitely
show its tail one day.
Innkeeper,
I advise you to
keep a close eye on your people.
Don't wait until one day
something slips up.
Alright.
Please, honoured guest.
Please leave.
Father, what's this?
What's wrong?
Did you do this?
No.
Not you?
Then what happened to his fingers?
Yes.
Quickly tell my father
what happened to your fingers?
Leave.
Get out!
Why is it that every time
something like this happens,
Father always
suspects me first?
I understand now.
Because in Father's heart,
I am such an evil person.
I would do evil things.
That's why you won't take me home,
won't let me see Grandfather and Grandmother,
and insist on keeping me in such a
godforsaken place
running an inn.
You're afraid I might harm
your family,
aren't you?
That's not true.
Then please, my dear Father,
tell me.
If it's not like that,
then what is it?
You are my family.
Then who would be afraid of their own family?
I'm not afraid of you.
You are.
You've always been afraid of me
and you're getting more and more afraid.
Father,
since you don't like me anyway,
why don't you let me go?
Just like my brother.
Once I leave,
I will never
cause you trouble again.
No.
You can't go anywhere.
It's not safe out there.
This is your home.
Home?
Fine.
Then we'll just stay here.
But if
someone else gets hurt,
Father, don't you dare
blame it on me.
Yanqiu, you're awake.
Banxia.
You're here.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Was it because of that wine?
The innkeeper's daughter just came by.
She said the wine is called Fubai Wine.
After drinking it,
you could see the person you miss the most.
So you know everything.
That's right.
The world is truly vast,
full of wonders.
Over the past six months,
I've really broadened my horizons.
Not only have I seen demons,
but I've also tasted
this Fubai Wine.
Do you know how clear it was?
It wasn't like a normal drunken dream.
It's just like it's real.
She's right in front of me,
talking to me,
laughing and chatting,
so vivid and lifelike.
It's as if...
It's as if she never
left at all.
Banxia,
do you want to try it?
I'll ask for a bit more.
Just a little,
and you can see your parents.
Give it a try.
Yanqiu,
you can't stay here any longer.
Grandmother, Uncle and Aunt
are still at home.
You haven't gone back for so long,
they're very worried about you.
Home?
How can home be as good as here?
Here, I have Manniang with me.
You've already been here
for half a month.
It's all because of this Fubai Wine.
Come to your senses.
Manniang.
Chi Xue.
Why is it here again?
Didn't we come from here?
Is anyone there?
Nine Lives.
Banxia.
Xuanye.
What are you looking for?
I thought I just saw Nine Lives.
Let's go back first.
The culprit should be
that servant you mentioned.
Then let's catch him!
Who cares if it's him or not?
Let's bring him in first,
and we'll find out after interrogation.
No matter how tough he is,
he can't be tougher than the torture instruments in prison.
Shopkeeper Feng Tian
won't allow us to make a move.
According to Physician Jiu,
his martial arts skills are impressive.
And that servant,
he's not an ordinary person either.
There's more than one servant in this inn.
There's also that Wuniang.
I always felt she was strange.
Don't forget,
there's also a Cat Demon lurking in the shadows.
So,
if we can't beat them,
let's retreat
and go back to get more help.
Do you think they'll
obediently wait for us
to come back and catch them?
My cousin is still here.
He's addicted to Fubai Wine.
For the time being,
he definitely won't be willing to leave.
Fubai Wine?
I was in such a hurry earlier
that I forgot to tell you.
I found out that this inn
is selling a kind of wine,
called the Fubai Wine.
It's said that after drinking it,
you could see the person you miss the most.
My brother is like this now
because he drank this wine
and became immersed in heartache of
missing my sister-in-law.
That's why he refuses to leave.
We dare not act rashly.
I believe they won't either.
I'll go back first to settle
Yan Li's body.
We'll discuss the rest later.
Xuanye,
I don't think the Cat Demon
is with them.
I got lost in the courtyard earlier,
and it seems the Cat Demon
guided me back.
Are you sure your cousin
was drinking Fubai Wine?
I'm certain.
You've heard of this wine too?
Yanzi,
I've failed you.
You've only been married for a year,
and just had a son.
How can I face
your family?
You're an only child.
It's all my fault.
I should have gone instead.
Let's solve this case quickly
and avenge Yan Li.
Right.
Revenge.
I've finally found you.
Catch.
No fun at all.
Take it away.
You're only giving it to me because you don't want it anymore?
I need to go out for a while.
Protect Banxia well.
Don't leave her side, understand?
Where are you going?
None of your business.
[Xin]
Banxia is very worried about you.
This wine is called Fubai Wine.
It uses abalone shell and cornelian cherry as its guiding ingredients,
supplemented with wheat bran,
and brewed through fermentation.
The recipe is simple,
but the extraction method varies.
However, once you know
the key,
it's not difficult to brew.
If you like it,
I can teach you
the extraction method.
This way, when you return to Nanyang City,
you can brew it yourself.
Why?
You think I'm here to persuade you?
I've been drinking this wine for six years.
What right do I have to persuade you?
Do you know?
When I was young,
I offended an enemy.
I couldn't catch him,
and he escaped.
Later,
he hurt my family,
infecting them with demon poison
and making them lose their minds.
In their heads,
it was left with the desire to kill.
I had no choice
but to kill them all.
My parents, my elder brother,
and the servants in our house,
all died by my hand.
This wine
is indeed a good thing.
All these years,
I've relied on this wine
to get by.
Whenever I feel that
life is unbearable,
whenever I miss my family,
it could always deceive me,
making me believe
that nothing has changed.
Every time before I go home,
I always take a few sips
at the doorstep.
Then I push open the door,
and everyone's there.
You're a bit different from me.
I've long been
a lone wolf.
Life and death are up to fate,
no one cares.
But you're different.
You still have family,
family waiting for you to return.
In my home,
there's no one left.
Don't wait until
your family is gone.
By then, it will be too late
to regret.
Qiu.
Manniang.
I have to leave.
I'm fine, you don't need to help me.
I can walk on my own.
What's wrong with you all?
I can walk.
Chi Xue.
Where's Xuanye?
I don't know.
Xuanye told me to
protect you without leaving your side for a single moment.
Xuanye.
What's wrong?
I'm different from them.
I know it's not real.
What do you mean?
Father.
Slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Drink some water, Father.
Daughter.
Father carved a little wooden doll.
Do you like it?
See if it looks like you.
It does.
It does, doesn't it?
Wuniang likes it.
Wuniang wants to give Father a massage on the back.
Alright.
Father, you've worked hard.
Not hard at all.
[Cuixiao Hall]
I've warned you.
Don't get close to him,
nor
appear in front of me.
This is the last time.
If you dare ruin my plans again,
be wary
that I'll take away
the few lives you have left.